Because it's being created within an activity, it can be
因为它在activity里面创建，所以它可以
terminated as simply as rotating the phone into a different
被很轻松的终止，例如把手机旋转到另一个
orientation. So, should only ever be used for tasks whose
方向。 因此，应该只在这种情况下使用它，就是在那些
lifecycle is tied to the host activity, and is expected
生命周期和activity绑定的任务上，而且是期望
to run for only a second or two. On mobile,
只是运行一到两秒的事件。在移动设备上，
it's unwise to assume that even the most trivial network
假定网络访问迅速可达，即便是对于次要事件而言，也是
access is going to happen quickly. So a better approach
不明智的，所以较好的方法是
would be to use a service. An application component without
使用一个“service”，一个没有用户界面的应用程序组件
the UI that's less likely to be
很小可能会被
interrupted. Possibly scheduled using an inexact repeating alarm.
中断。最可能的情况是，在调度所使用的一个不准确的时钟的时候（时钟中断）。
Even better, Android has a specialized solution know
更佳的是，Android有一个特定的解决方案，叫做
as Async Adapter. And it's designed especially to schedule
异步Adapter，而且它专门设计用来调度你的
your background data syncs as efficiently as possible. Better
背景（后台？）数据的同步，并尽可能的高效。
still would be using Google Cloud Messaging. This lets
当然使用谷歌云消息系统是最好的。它可以用来
you notify your Async Adapter of changes on the
通知你的异步Adpater，服务器端有变化发生。
server side. So you're only ever initiating network requests
此时，你只需要在app里面初始化网络请求，
from your app when you know there's something to
当你知道服务器上有何种数据更新的时候。
be updated on the server. For now we're concentrating
这个时候，我们只需要集中在
on making our app work when it's in the foreground. But we'll return to
处理前景任务上，使得我们的app能够运作。 稍后，我们仍然会回过头看看
look at these approaches to invisibly updating
那些能够在背景任务上透明化的更新你的
your app from the background a little
app的方法，
later. For now, keep in mind that the Refresh button and the new thread
目前，只需要记住刷新按钮以及创建新的线程的
solution is just a place holder while we hook up the rest of the app.
解决方案只是一种，当我们需要和app的其余部分相关联时，所使用的连接点。